<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BizCom Management Services PTE. LTD.’s Blog</title><description>Bizcom is a boutique accounting firm with a proven track record providing specialist support for tax, accounting and business advisory services to Singapore &amp; Malaysia companies. Get in touch with us for your accounting needs. We would love to hear from you!</description><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/</link><item><title>Business Acumen &amp; Association</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/business-acumen-association</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/business-acumen-association</guid><description>Partnering with an industry-recognized firm gives credibility to your business.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cost Efficiency</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/cost-efficiency</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/cost-efficiency</guid><description>BizCom offers quality services by professionals at a fraction of the costs so you save money for your business.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Industry Expertise</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/industry-expertise</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/industry-expertise</guid><description>Our team is equipped with valuable knowledge and years of experience to help you and your business make sound financial decisions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Professional Advice &amp; Practices</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/professional-advice-practices</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/professional-advice-practices</guid><description>BizCom’s qualified team of professionals brings only the best business practices and advice to all our clients, so we can help you grow and organize your business finances.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Audit Services Singapore</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/audit-services</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/audit-services</guid><description>An audit is required for all companies in Singapore unless your company is exempted from audit.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bookkeeping Services Singapore</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/bookkeeping-services</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/bookkeeping-services</guid><description>Timely and accurate financial information is imperative for any business or company to maintain a competitive advantage in today’s dynamic business environment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Company Common Seal</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/company-common-seal</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/company-common-seal</guid><description>The common seal creates an embossing effect when pressure is applied. The seal is usually required for legal documents, share certificates, deeds and major contracts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Company Income Tax Singapore</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/company-income-tax</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/company-income-tax</guid><description>Every business decision entails a tax implication. As such, obtaining effective and accurate tax advice is crucial to your business operations. Given the ever-increasing complexity of tax regulations, finding the right tax consultant to guide you through is vital to any successful business.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Company Incorporation Malaysia</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/company-incorporation-malaysia</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/company-incorporation-malaysia</guid><description>The Companies Act, 1965 governs all companies in Malaysia. The Act stipulates that a person must register a company with Companies Commission of Malaysia (CCM) (in Bahasa Malaysia as Suruhanjaya Syarikat Malaysia) prior to engaging in any business activities in Malaysia.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Company Incorporation Singapore</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/company-incorporation-singapore</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/company-incorporation-singapore</guid><description>Singapore has always enjoyed a great reputation as an ideal venue for Business Incorporation due to the following.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Compilation Services Singapore</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/compilation-services</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/compilation-services</guid><description>Your company may be exempted from audit if it is a Private Exempt Company (“EPC”). EPC means that no corporate shareholder in the company and the number of shareholders in the company is not more than 20. In addition.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corporate Secretarial Services Singapore</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/corporate-secretarial-services</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/corporate-secretarial-services</guid><description>Every company must have at least one secretary appointed within 6 months from the date of incorporation. However, a Singapore private company, other than that required under the Companies Act, need not appoint a professionally qualified company secretary.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goods &amp; Service Tax Singapore</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/goods-services-tax</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/goods-services-tax</guid><description>The Singapore Goods and Services Tax (GST) is a tax charged on the supply of goods and services made in Singapore and on the importation of goods into Singapore. The current rate for GST is 7%.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nominee Director Services Singapore</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/nominee-director-services</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/nominee-director-services</guid><description>Under the Singapore Companies Act, a Private Limited Company in Singapore must have at least 1 local resident director, which is made up of either.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Payroll Services Singapore</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/payroll-services</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/payroll-services</guid><description>One of the most important tasks for all businesses is the preparation of payroll and payment of salary. This process can be further complicated and made more time-consuming with additional components such as benefits, allowances, deductions, government remittance, and much more. This is why many SMEs opt to outsource their payroll function to third-party accounting firms.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Income Tax Singapore</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/personal-income-tax</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/personal-income-tax</guid><description>Singapore’s Personal Income Tax structure is one of the friendliest and most competitive in the world. The tax year is from 1st January to 31 December in each calendar year and income is assessed on a preceding year basis.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strike Off Company Singapore</title><link>https://bizcom.vercel.app/strike-off-company</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://bizcom.vercel.app/strike-off-company</guid><description>A company may apply to the Accounting and Corporate Regulatory Authority (ACRA) to strike its name offÂ the Register pursuant to Section 344 of the Companies Act.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>